Guide to the Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, Photograph Albums Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Volume IV
  - Page 25
    - 1163-64. [Sliding into base] (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1165. [Baseball]--hit (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1166. [Baseball]--Felsey, Reilly, Shear, Osborn, Beddy (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Page 26
    - 1167. Reilly tagged out at plate--Brown game (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1168. [Baseball]--Y. Stevens, Watrous, Mudge, Shear, Hunter, Pendelton, Hunter, Oman, Ripley, Gile (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1169. [Baseball]--Penn game, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1170. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1171. [Baseball]--Way, Carl (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1172. [Baseball]--Haznes (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1173. [Baseball]--calisthenics (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1174. Cornish--safe at third (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1175. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1176. Swimming Association (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Page 27
    - 1177. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1178. [Baseball]--Grossius, 1915S (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1179. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1180. [Baseball]--Mudge (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1181. [Baseball]--Middlebrook (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1182. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1183. [Baseball]--Magee (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1184. [Baseball]--Gurney, Y 1916 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1185. [Baseball]--Swihart, Burdett (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1186. [Baseball] Carl, Goodell, Tilney, Rush, Osborn, Beckert, Campbell, Shear (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Page 28
    - 1187. [Baseball]--L. Walsh, Y 1916 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1188. [Baseball]--seventh inning (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1189. [Baseball]--Arnold, 1915S (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1190. [Baseball]--Slimmon, Coley, News vs. Heelers,1913 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1191. [Baseball]--Reilly (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1192-93. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - 1194. [Baseball]--Osborn, Stevens, Beckon, Thomas, Ripley, Carl, Thompson, Campbell, Goodell, Pendleton, Cobb, Shear (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Page 29
    - 1195. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1196. [Baseball]--1916 vs. Springfield (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1197. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1198. [Baseball]--Providence (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1199. [Baseball]--Hargham (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1200. [Baseball]--Blossom (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1201. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1202. [Baseball]--Rumelin (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Page 30
    - 1203. [Baseball]--Gile (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1204. Reilly--[Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1205-07. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1208. [Baseball]--Vaughn (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1209. [Baseball]--Rumelin (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1210. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Page 31
    - 1211. [Football]--Wilson (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 1212-1214. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 1215. [Football]--Huntington (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 1216-1218. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Page 32
    - 1219. [Football]--Talbot (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - 1220-1227. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Page 33
    - 1228. L. Carter [pole vault] (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1229. Mamauguin Picnic, 1916--Wiles, Viele, Morris, King, Mulligan, Closson, Mead, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1230. [Children playing with tinker-toy] (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1231. Dilley, Healy, Moss, Longstreth, Peck (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Page 34
    - 1232. [Statue of fallen Indian] (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1233. Guenther and Scarborough shooting craps, May 1916 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1234. [Winter day] (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - 1235. [Walks, from above] (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Page 35
    - 1236-37. Commencement, June 1916 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1238. William Lyon Phelps, Granville, Barker--testing the acoustics of the Bowl for Iphigenia (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1239. Loghridte, 1914S (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1240. Hanes, Middlebrook, Easton--Yale outfield, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Page 36
    - 1241. The shoes I wore out (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1242. R. Matthews, 1915 [broad jump] (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1243. Lounsbury Funeral, 1915 [Elm Street] (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1244. Class exercises, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1245. College Street from Osborn, June 1916 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - 1246. First reunion of 1916--Leiper, Boardman, P. Proctor, A. Proctor, Barney, Oliver, Russell, Cary (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Page 37
    - 1247. Tap Day, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1248. Arrival, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1249. 10 degrees below (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1250. March 1916, Bassett, Vance, Bachmann, King, Grubb (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Page 38
    - 1251. Chapel lets out (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1252. Taft corner (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1253. Hall of Fame (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - 1254. H. W. Hobson, M.P. Noues, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Page 39
    - 1255. Grand Theatre burns, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1256. Omega Lamda Chi, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1257. Titlman, Anderson, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1258. Osborn reference library (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1259. 1915, Cary, Miller, Zahner, Lane, Toole, Eastman, Mather, Enwright, Baber, Beach (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1260. Fagan, Walsh, Washburn (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Page 40
    - 1261. Fifth Avenue, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1262. Treasure chest rehearsing, Tenatone, Leiper (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1263. Willstein--orchestra in Commons (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - 1264. Enwright, Levy, Brady (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Page 41
    - 1265-1272. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Page 42
    - 1273. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - 1274. [Football]--Shelden (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - 1275-76. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Page 43
    - 1277. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1278. [Football]--Scovit (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1279-80. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1281. [Football]--Performance on the field (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1282-84. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Page 44
    - 1285. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1286. [Football]--Shelden 1916S (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1287-91. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1292. [Football team jogging] (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - 1293. [Football team getting on tram] (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Page 45
    - 1294-97. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1298. [Football]--Loughridge (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1299-1302. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Page 46
    - 1304. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1305. [Football]--Wagoner (cheerleader) (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1306. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1307. [Football]--Camb (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1308. [Football]--Howe (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1309-12. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1313. [Football]--Bomeister (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1314-18. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - 1303. [Football]--Yates (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Page 47
    - 1319. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1320. [Football]--Gilfillain, 1915S (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1321. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1322. [Football]--Storming the field (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1323. [Football]--Guernsey, 1916S (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1324-25. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1326. [Football]--P. Baker (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1327. [Football]--Yale-Harvard, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1328. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1329. [Football]--Philbin (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1330-31. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Page 48
    - 1332. [Football]--Spaulding (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1333. [Football]--Cooney (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - 1334-40. [Football] (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Page 49
    - 1341. G. W. Goodwin (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - 1342. W.J. Freeman, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Page 50
    - 1343. Pierrot men, Omega Lamda Chi (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - 1344. Cercle francais play, Amelia Walker (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - 1345. [Hurdles] (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - 1346. Signing up with the Battery for intensive work early in April 1917 [huge line across campus to Durfee] (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Page 51
    - 1347. Yale 49, Colgate 0, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1348. Decoration Day parade, May 30, 1917 [Elm Street looking toward Broadway] (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1349. 1854 going to Alumni Dinner, June 1917 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1350. Faculty Battery cheering Danford and Potter upon their dismissal, Note turf, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1351. Juniors snowballing, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Page 52
    - 1352. Next to Yale Field (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1353. Le Gore tackling dummy [football] (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1354. L.L. Bredin, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - 1355-56. Spring falls, West Rock Ridge, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Page 53
    - 1357-58. [Fencing] (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1359. [Track] (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1360. 1914 seniors running to the other end of the panorama (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1361. [Track] (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1362. Audience applauding a stroke of Williams [golf] (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1363. Oler at 1913 Harvard intercollegiates (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1364. F. Tuttle and T. Smith, 1915 rehearsing for --Quentin Durward--, the 1915 Spring play (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1365. Trap shooters (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Page 54
    - 1366. Freshmen taking gym work (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1367. 1916 as sophomores, pitching nickels (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1368. Wrestling match in University trials, 1914, Hayries vs. Wallace (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1369. 220 dash in 1913 fall meet (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1370. Intercollegiates at Cambridge, 1913, start of half mile (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1371. Hockey squad starting on a run --And a little child shall lead them (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1372. 1916 vs. 1917 wrestling match (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1373. [Hockey team on run] (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - 1374. Gym leaders 1913, Anderson, Foster (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Page 55
    - 1375. Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 1376. Taft's reception, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 1377. Memorial Day parade, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 1378. Levy, Fagan, Goodhue, Lloyd (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Page 56
    - 1379. J. Stewart, Levy, Guernsey, Titlman, Cowles, Chism, Rosenberg, Rubinson, Caldwell, Walsh (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 1380. Gargoyle on boat house (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 1381. 1916 North from Phelps (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - 1382. 1916 [spring fun on roller skates] (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Page 57
    - 1383. [Daily News]--Heeler's room (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1384. [Daily News]--Coley, O.N. (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1385. [Daily News]--MacDonald (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1386. [Daily News]--Linotype (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1387. [Daily News]--Printing (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1388. [Daily News]--in PO Boxes (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1389. [Daily News]--Contributors (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1390. Signs of spring (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1391. Cooney (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1392. Osborn corner (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1393. Opposite Dwight (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1394. Marting (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1395. Unbroken windows (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1396. Out of chapel (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1397. Diabolo (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1398. Spring overcoats (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1399. Sunday chapel (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1400. News cart (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Page 58
    - 1401. Night scene (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1402. Westville (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1403. Woolsey statue (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1404. Greenwich (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1405. Waterbury Road (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1406. Old Library (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1407. Joe Grubb (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1408. New Haven Engine (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1409. Snow plow (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1410. Tender (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1411. New Haven yards (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1412. Greenwich (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1413. University of Pennsylvania triangle (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1414. Masquerading (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1415. Delaware River (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1416. Sophomore quarters (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1417. Kreider in physics (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1418. Veasy (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - 1419. University of Pennsylvania triangle (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Page 59
    - 1420. Boardman, Barney, R. Proctor, Cary, June 1917 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1421. R.O.T.C. fires 21 guns at dedication of Armory, June 1917 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1422. Graduates listening to Danford (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1423. R.O.T.C. and graduates by Ledyard Flagpole (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Page 60
    - 1424. Yale Naval Training Unit on Decoration Day, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1425. Wiley (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1426. Setting up exercises at 6:30 AM in Grub Street, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1427. Goodwin, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1428. Higgenbotham (killed flying 2/23/1918) (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - 1429. Tap Day, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Page 61
    - 1430. Hampton riding Crocker (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1431. Lounsbury Funeral, 1915, Taft, Pierson, Roosevelt, Hadley, Chittenden (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1432. Prexy and Mrs. Hadley, H.W. Hobson, 1914 [on a boar] (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1433. Tap Day, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1434. Elm and High Streets after cleaning, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Page 62
    - 1435. Crocker, Y 1916 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1436. Tuttle and T. Smith rehearsing--"Quentin Durward-- (see picture 1364) (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1437. R. S. Oliver (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - 1438. Posture after standing high jump, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Page 63
    - 1439. Omega Lamda Chi baseball game, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1440. Hobo band (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1441. Pavlova and Nijinsky at Brown game, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1442. [Omega Lamda Chi?] (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1443. Omega Lamda Chi--Danvels as hobo, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1444. Duplicate of 1441 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1445. [Parade--Omega Lamda Chi?] (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Page 64
    - 1446. Four rush at Penn (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1447. [Bladder ball] (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1448. Omega Lamda Chi, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1449. St. Patrick's Day at Princeton (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1450. Whiffenpoof float, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1451. Fall, 1912 [group] (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - 1452. 1913 [costumed baseball game] (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Page 65
    - 1453. Before Sunday chapel, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 1454. Execution of Villa (Porter), 1915, Caldwell, Cary, Baber, King, Johnson, White, Eckmann, Leonard, Innes, Aldrich, Leiber, Porter, Felty, Walsh, Levy (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 1455. Rushing 1917 candidates, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 1456. [a canyon] (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Page 66
    - 1457. Tossing nickels--White, Bachmann, Taylor, Gulliver, Jones, McGonnell, Perry, Leiber, Williams, Eddy, Booth, Goodwin, Miller, Grubb, Thomas, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 1458. Freeman, Carrington, Gardner, Roberts, Tener, Polhamus, R. Crocker (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 1459. Bull and assistant coaches (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - 1460. Crocker tapped by Castles, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Page 67
    - 1461. Jepson organ recital on Sunday at Woolsey (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1462. Walter Camp (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1463. [Entrance to Oval] (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1464. Commons from Wall Street (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1465. Eastern side of campus (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1466. Marting, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1467. Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1468. Memorial and Woodbridge Halls (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Page 68
    - 1469. Dwight, Wright, Durfee--Northwestern corner of campus (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1470. The 1914 Steps--Baber, Luiper, Galliard, Bensom, Perry (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1471. Taylor Hall and Dai Mission Library (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1472. Practice parade before Brown game, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1473. [Interior] of Adee Boathouse--showing sculls (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1474. Gymnasium laundry (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - 1475. [Portals of Bowl under construction] (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Page 69
    - a. Benjamin, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - b. Osborn Plaza (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - c. Sigma Delta Psi trials, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - d. [Miller Gateway] (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - e. Penn wrestling (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Page 70
    - f. Drew S. Calf wins 100 at Penn, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - g. Crowd at Taft Hotel, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - h-i. [a young man in Berkeley Oval] (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - j. trip (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - k. Littlefield, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Page 71
    - 1476. Omega Lamda Chi, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1477. Omega Lamda Chi, 1915--"Chaplin movie (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1478. 1914 men--"Martin, Cooney (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1479. 1915, Queal, Young (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Page 72
    - 1480. 1915, Fitts, Mulqueen, Taylor, Miller, Goodwin, Jones (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1481-82. Calf, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1483. Finals in Lampson (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1484. Conish, Lane, Smith, Torgon, Davidson, Johnson, Goss, Taylor, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Page 73
    - 1485. Campus football, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1486. Stakes, Dwight, Hadley, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1487. [winter] (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Page 74
    - 1488. Graham, Burnett (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1489. Dwight Hall (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1490. Smashing windows, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1491. Roberts, Howe, Torson, Proctor, Phenix, Polhamus, Haren (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1492. Lacrosse practice (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1493. Hellier, Roberts, Perry, Hampton, 1914-15 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Page 75
    - 1494. Calcium Light Night, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 1495. Wiles, Morris, Viele, Smith, Richards (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 1496. Academic procession, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 1497. Book and Snake Tomb (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Page 76
    - 1498. Lloyd, Fagan (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 1499. [Dog] (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 1500. Circus Day crowd, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - 1501. Tap Day, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Page 77
    - 1502. Reg Field (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - 1503. The Battery, May 1916 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - 1504-05. Field exercises (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Page 78
    - 1506. Field exercises (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - 1507. Tossing Otis 1919 in a blanket (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - 1508. [Airplane over New Haven Harbor breakwater] (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - 1509. May 1916, Thomas, Wiles, Hume, Mulligan, Morris, Bolton, Leete [hoops and skates] (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Page 79
    - 1510. Crew--Gore, Bugbee, Denegre, Philbin, Freeman, Coe, Henry, Snowden, Barnum (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1511. Crew--Snowden, Kirby (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1512. [Crew]--Gore, Plimpton, Denegre, Philbin, Jenkinson, Denmen, Lippincott, Snowden, Barnum (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1513. [Crew] (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1514. [Crew]--Safford (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1515. [Crew] (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1516. [Crew]--Frank, Plimpton (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1517. [Crew]--Omayn, Rogers (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1518. [Crew] (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Page 80
    - 1519-20. [Crew] (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1521. [Crew]--Spring Regatta, 1913, Krimmon Boar (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1522. [Crew]--Fall Regatta (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1523. [Crew]--First freshmen at Ferry (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - 1524-25. [Crew] (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Page 81
    - 1526. [Baseball]--Brown (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1527. [Baseball]--Reilly (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1528. [Baseball]--Rechendorfer (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1529. [Baseball]--Watrous (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1530. [Baseball]--Third base (Cameramen) (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Page 82
    - 1531. [Baseball]--Riddell, Foster (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1532. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1533. [Baseball]--Dyer (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1534. [Baseball]--Virginia, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1535. [Baseball] (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1536. [Baseball]--1916 freshmen (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1537. [Baseball]--R.W. Robbins, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1538. [Baseball]--Case 1914 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - 1539. [Baseball] Henter, Pop Foster (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Page 83
    - 1540. [Winter night] (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1541. 1914 at play (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1542. Alumni Day 1914 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1543. 1916 watches tussle (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1544. A hand organ and monkey draw well (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Page 84
    - 1545. 1915, Graves, Noyes, Panphor (died 1917), Williams, Grisholm (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1546. Cornelius the Laundry Man (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1547. Sheff town (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - 1548. Iphigenia in Tauris (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Page 85
    - 1549. [Umbrella in stadium] (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 1550-51. Boys receiving tickets to Brown game [on New Haven Green, by flagpole] (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 1552-55. [Football practice] (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Page 86
    - 1556. [Football game] (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 1557. [Line up] (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 1558. [Football game] (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 1559. [Bowl--"under construction] (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - 1560-63. [Football game] (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Page 87
    - 1564. Lounsbury Funeral, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1565. Roosevelt, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1566. Looking east from Taft Hotel (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1567. [Baseball game] (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Page 88
    - 1568. 1914, S. Miller, Lloyd, Fagan (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1569. 1914 seniors in Wright Court (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1570. Accident in Candidate's Race, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1571. Sheff Society Orchestra--N. Graves--"Manager, CW Smith, Loske, McNulty (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Page 89
    - 1572. Treadway--220 dash, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1573. ½ mile--Willisbrooks Spring Meet, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1574. Johnstone (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1575. 1913 Spring Meet--Revell, Blackmer, Cornell, Ainsworth, Cowles, Ricketts (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - 1576. Three hurdlers (Box 3, Folder 127)
- Volume V (?)
  - Page 1
    - 1577. Whiffenpoof celebration, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1578. Old Campus (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1579. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1580. The sundial, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1581. [Old Infirmary] (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Page 2
    - 1582. Durfee Hall (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1583. Woolsey (statue) (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1584. Plow (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1585. Dwight Hall (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1586. Lawrance Hall (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - 1587. Connecticut Hall (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Page 3
    - 1588. From Durfee (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1589. Religious conference, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1590. Chapel St. (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1591. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1592. Work on the Bowl (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1593. Osborn Corner (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1594. Rush--Southern California (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1595. Day Mission Library (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1596. Wright Dedication (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1597. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Page 4
    - 1598. Wright Dedication (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1599. Wright Dedication (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1600-01. Wright Dedication--front row: Jones, Dwight, Hadley, Wright (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - 1602. Porter (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Page 5
    - 1603. Sunday morning--first from left: Crocker, third from left: Dudley, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1604. Woolsey statue (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1605. Dwight Chapel (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1606. Building the rink (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1607. Concrete mixer at the Bowl (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - 1608. [unidentified] (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Page 6
    - 1609. Porter Gateway, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 130)